AZAD KHAN

7355425402 • azadkhan9452@gmail.com • LinkedIn

Summary

Specializes in contributing to a highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions, and determining customer satisfaction. Web applications are designed and developed across multiple APIs, third-party integrations, and databases. Passionate and hardworking with a passion for efficiently performing tasks.

Experience

1. Software Developer Intern, 05/2022 to 09/2022

Mcsam - Gurgoan, India

- Partnered with company mentor to learn best practices in software design.
- Fix bugs and errors in application software both frontend and backend
- Used development tools such as Django rest framework and Postman regularly.
- Analyzed source code to identify and rectify potential functionality issues.
- Utilize such technologies as Python, Django rest framework, Angular, Html & CSS, and
- MySQL to develop new functionality in the application.
- 2. **DevOps Engineer Intern**, 02/2022 to 04/2022

Ismile Technologies - Bolingbrook Illinois, United States

- Quickly learned new skills and applied them to daily tasks.
- Carried out day-to-day duties accurately and efficiently.
- Hands-on experience in Terraform.
- Learn AZ-900: Microsoft Azure Fundamentals.
- Translating requirements and functional specifications into Data.
- Infrastructure as service(IaS).

Skills

- Python
- Java
- Html, CSS
- Angular
- Django Rest Framework

- Azure
- Postman API
- Terraform
- MySQL
- GitHub

Project

- 1. Image Blurring and Deblurring with Noise Removal, 08/2021 to 04/2022
 - I have taken Kaggle dataset high-resolution Images and used Gaussian blur for adding noise and reduce the resolution
 - Use such technologies as Python, Matplotlib, Pandas, and OpenCV.
 - Apply SRCNN architecture for deblurring the blurred Images
- 2. **Rental Website**, 02/2021 to 05/2021
 - Website in which Users can register and search perfect place to live, rent a house and buy a plot.
 - Build this webpage using Html, CSS, and JavaScript.

Education

B.TECH: Computer Science & Engineering, 07/2022

GALGOTIAS COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING & TECHNOLOGY - Greater Noida, Uttar Pradesh

INTERMEDIATE: PCM, 06/2017

J. SHIKSHAN S. I. C. JAMON - Amethi, Uttar Pradesh

This is to declare that all the above entries are true to the best of my knowledge.

AZAD KHAN